# **Matthew Lewis**

Address 9 Tredwell Close Phone (+44) 7909977421

London, SW2 3JZ Email matthew@mglewis.co.uk

Website mglewis.co.uk

# **Personal Profile**

Enthusiastic software developer and systems engineer. Experience with Java, CI amoungst a variety platforms and systems. Has been known to develop software for fun in his spare time.

Likely to be found on evenings and weekends bouldering, playing football or watching cricket.

# **Employment History**

### 2015 - **UBS - Authorised Officer**

Software Engineer and Product Owner

- Responsible for a portfolio of custom and 3rd party applications.
- Managed team of offshore software developers.
- Delivered IBM Business Process Manager to the UBS environment.

Technologies: Java, Jenkins, Linux, Git, Swift, Nexus, Shell, Oracle

#### 2013 - 2014 **UBS - Non Officer**

Software Engineer

- Sucessfully delivered a complete stack upgrade of EMC Documentum 7.1.
- Developed a number of high performance custom Java components.
- Drove team adoption of best practices: VC, CI, Automated Testing, Release Management.

Technologies: Java, Jenkins, Linux, Solaris, Tomcat, Websphere, Ant, Shell, Oracle

#### 2011 - 2013 UBS - Graduate Trainee

Analyst

- Developed VBA and Tableau reporting systems.
- Designed and implemented a series of automated tools for use by remote support teams.

Technologies: VBA, Tableau, SQL, BASH, Atlassian Suite.

# **Education**

#### 2008 - 2011 University of Bristol

2:1 Computer Science BSc (with Hons)